Hello.
Welcome back.
And this lesson we are going to install our esteemed Thatta to Cuba makes.
So this is the complete download package.
I'm going to right.
Click over here to extract it or extract here.
And it's Finnish extract in order will click over here.
There's a content interest in a may have downloaded the.
I may have done that, the Mac OS version, so I'm sure you downloaded a Windows version, so I'm going
to download a Windows version.
No, see, OK.
No.
The download package comes with the Windows version.
The Mac version.
And the Linux version.
The reason why I think it's just a Mac version is does the only folder I see over here.
I'm going to sort of create a new photo here, hear a call in my in my downloads for DLC Cube Imex.
And I'm going to extract into the fold rather than have it mixed up with everything else over here.
Just fix this clean up.
Yeah, okay.
Just bear with me.
So this the Cuba mix.
Come over here now.
Oh, extract it in here.
OK, so we have the Windows version here.
The mock version and a Linux double click in the Windows version here to install it.
So, yes, over here.
OK.
It says the application requires Java runtime environment.
This.
So if you don't have Java runtime environment, you would have to install that.
So that's a different computer than the one I use every.
So I don't have Java here.
So I would have to install this Java runtime environment.
GRV.
Okay.
So it's bringing me to the Java Web site to download a GRV.
Okay, download.
It's open in Internet Explorer, so just bear with me.
Click here to download, click it to save.
Click here to run it.
Install.
It's installed in.
Okay.
Right.
See what happens next.
So I'm gonna go back to our makes row.
Try to install it again.
Double click, this is team 32.
Cuba makes five.
Java hasn't completed installation yet.
She wants to leave the Java the show.
Let's see.
Gerri still running.
Do it's currently installing is just taking a bit a bit longer than I expected.
So let's wait for it.
It says it says you have successfully installed Java.
Okay.
Should be fine, though, if we're still unable to get access to it.
We may have to restart the computer.
Okay.
I mean, stalling.
Keep that makes.
Now click.
Yes, right here.
OK.
For LA it started and a click next over here.
I've read this before so I just click to accept it next and then step this.
So you can kinda take a look at the um the privacy policy as well as the terms of use before you accept
it like this.
Over here.
A click over here.
And this installation foda or keep it the same click next target.
Right.
Uh, it says away the target directory will be created a click.
Okay.
And a click next to over here.
And this is installed and now it's gonna take a while.
It's still in stolen.
Okay, so I'm going to click next.
And then I'm going to click done over here.
The installation is complete.
Right.
So next, I'm going to install the keep IP.
That's my downloads folder.
I'm going to create a folder to extract it into a Korda's Cube IDC Raw.
I'm simply going to crack the Kubi into this folder and then extract it over here.
It's a structure in.
Still extracting.
Don't extract him.
I'm going to install it by double click on this over here.
Quick, yes, over here.
Click next over here.
I agree, but keep the, um, the destination forward at the same click next.
Click it or kick it.
Oh.
Keep everything here.
The same next.
And it started.
It's still in stolen.
This would take a while, so I just post.
Okay.
The installation is complete.
Click next over here, create a desktop shortcut.
Click finish.
Right.
So that's all there is for this lesson.
And I shall see you in the next lesson.